<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>
      Drunken Siblings
    </title>
    <link>
      http://www.drunkensiblings.com
    </link>
    <desciption>
      We are a brother sister team wanting to share our thoughts and insights with you the Internet about anything we want really.
    </desciption>
    <item>
      <title>
        Episode 2 "Time's Edge"
      </title>
      <link>
        http://www.drunkensiblings.com/audio/Ep2TimesEdge.mp3
      </link>
      <guid>
        dsep001. http://www.drunkensiblings.com/audio/Ep2TimesEdge.mp3
      </guid>
      <pubDate>
        Wed, 4 Oct 2017 00:00:00 GMT
      </pubDate>
      <description>
        To stop her sadistic grandfather, Saul, and his band of time travelers from rewriting history, Kate must race to retrieve the CHRONOS keys before they fall into the Cyrists' hands. If she jumps back in time and pulls the wrong key--one that might tip off the Cyrists to her strategy--her whole plan could come crashing down, jeopardizing the future of millions of innocent people. Kate's only ally is Kiernan, who also carries the time-traveling gene. But their growing bond threatens everything Kate is trying to rebuild with Trey, her boyfriend who can't remember the relationship she can't forget.
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
        Episode 1 "Timebound"
      </title>
      <link>
        http://www.drunkensiblings.com/audio/Ep1Timebound.mp3
      </link>
      <guid>
        dsep001. http://www.drunkensiblings.com/audio/Ep1Timebound.mp3
      </guid>
      <pubDate>
        Sat, 17 Jun 2017 00:00:00 GMT
      </pubDate>
      <description>
        When Kate Pierce-Keller’s grandmother gives her a strange blue medallion and speaks of time travel, sixteen-year-old Kate assumes the old woman is delusional. But it all becomes horrifyingly real when a murder in the past destroys the foundation of Kate’s present-day life. Suddenly, that medallion is the only thing protecting Kate from blinking out of existence.
        Kate learns that the 1893 killing is part of something much more sinister, and her genetic ability to time travel makes Kate the only one who can fix the future. Risking everything, she travels back in time to the Chicago World’s Fair to try to prevent the murder and the chain of events that follows.
        Changing the timeline comes with a personal cost—if Kate succeeds, the boy she loves will have no memory of her existence. And regardless of her motives, does Kate have the right to manipulate the fate of the entire world?
      </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
